I did it!
Do you know where it is?
I don't know.
I'm wearing a red piano glove.
I'm just pretending to be a little.
We came to Disney Resort today.
Yeah!
We did a YouTube live streaming in July
and August this year.
We did a project to play darts.
We did a project to get a prize if we
hit the target.
We made a great success.
We went to a theme park in Chiba
Prefecture.
We made a great success.
We didn't have a problem.
I hope you don't look back at the
video.
We came to Disneyland today.
We'll enjoy it.
We'll go to the standby bus of the
Beauty and the Beast.
We'll go to the new area of the
attraction.
We'll go to the Beauty and the Beast
and Baymax.
We'll go to the standby bus of the
Beauty and the Beast and then go to
Baymax.
We'll have breakfast in the meantime.
We'll ride a roller coaster and enjoy
it.
Oharu can ride a roller coaster if
she's in Disney.
I can.
I'm afraid of it, but I can.
We can ride it.
Can you ride it, Aki?
I can.
I can't.
We can all ride it.
I'm worried about the coaster.
We have to turn it.
We can ride Baymax a lot.
I think so.
Let's enjoy it.
We'll go to find it.
Please subscribe to this channel!
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please subscribe to my channel!
From now it's time for monitoring,
Kazuma san.
Hello!
First, we are lining up for the first
attraction.
We are lining up!
It is an attraction that will be held
in 5 minutes.
That's right.
How many people will we be riding?
I don't know.
We are going to the hot spring.
We are going to be the Pirates of the
Caribbean.
We bought a black headband.
Let's go with a sense.
We are going to be there in 3 or 4
minutes.
I'm looking forward to it.
We are going to be there soon.
I'm excited.
I wonder how many people we can ride.
Please look forward to it.
We are going to ride. Bye bye.
We just boarded the Caribbean Pirates.
How was it?
We met Jack!
It was so real.
I felt my legs shaking.
I saw him so close.
It was fantastic.
We were all surprised at the first
moment.
It was a little unexpected.
There is Piglet.
Piglet, Eeyore,
and Yellow...
What was it?
Eeyore, Piglet,
and Children.
What was the pink one?
Piglet and Yellow...
Yellow...
I don't know about Yellow.
I forgot the name.
That's it.
Bye bye!
Hello!
We are in the second attraction.
We are going to ride the Jungle Cruise.
We are going to ride it in 20 minutes.
Jungle Cruise is like a ride on a
river.
It's fun to drive.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's have fun.
It's fun.
When we are walking, the cast wave
their hands.
It's a good world.
Everyone is in a peaceful world.
Only Julia's shoes are white.
Oh, really.
Everyone's shoes are black.
Black.
White.
Aki-chan's knee high is cute.
It's cold.
I want a popcorn bucket.
Yes, let's look for it.
There are cute popcorn buckets.
Monster jeans and Alice T-shirt are
cute.
Is there anything new?
I want something new.
I want a Christmas version of popcorn
bucket.
Is there a Christmas version?
I always buy a hat at Disney in the
morning and afternoon.
I always buy a popcorn bucket.
What should I do?
I want to buy it.
I'm just looking at it.
Julia is also wondering.
I bought a bag for my hand.
I should have bought a backpack.
If you buy a popcorn bucket, you'll be
two.
I'm going to buy it.
When I was a pirate in the Caribbean, I
felt like I was at Disney.
I felt like I was at a dreamland.
We'll go on a ride in a line.
See you.
Bye.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Itadakimasu!
It's so soft!
It's so good!
It's like a world class!
The way she talks is so good.
It was fun.
I think it was a little different.
I think so, too.
It's fun. It's been a while since I
came here.
I was surprised.
It's so fun.
Chicken is so delicious.
It's so delicious.
It's warm.
It's teriyaki chicken.
It's so tender.
I ate rice balls only in the morning.
So, I was hungry for the second
attraction.
And I want to eat churros.
I'm full.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat Little Green Man.
I want to eat the one that goes like
this.
Little Green Man.
Is it good?
I want to eat it.
I will look for it.
Maho.
The captain was funny.
He was dancing.
What was it?
He was putting his spear and his
thoughts on it.
Oh, the spear.
He was putting his thoughts on it.
It's my first time to do it.
It was fun.
Where are we going to ride now?
We are going to ride on the Big Thunder
Mountain!
This is the first ride of the Big
Thunder Mountain!
It's our first time riding on a roller
coaster.
Yeah, it's our first time riding on a
roller coaster.
Let's decide on a group.
2, 2, 2.
Thank you.
So, let's decide on a group while
recording.
2, 2.
Good Chopper.
We are climbing a mountain. Let's say
goodbye to Good Chopper.
We just said goodbye. Let's say
goodbye.
We said goodbye.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Kanamin, Tio, Oharu, Hitoka, Akikane,
and Sano.
We are the only three.
Where should I go?
Go ahead.
We are going to enjoy the festival.
It was fun!
Thank you!
We rode it!
We went inside the tunnel and went
outside.
Every time we went outside, Piyo was
like,
Everyone!
We were like that.
Even when no one was there, we were
like,
Everyone!
We were waiting.
We were like people who were waiting.
We were there, but there was nothing.
We were the ones who waved the most
among the people who rode it today.
It was the best.
But there were people who waved their
hands.
I waved my hands.
I danced the square dance.
It was fun.
We stretched our hands and held the
safety bar.
We held the safety bar and just when we
were climbing, we were like,
We tied the safety bar of the hand
called Kanamin.
We tied it.
Until it was over.
We are going to ride the next ACT6 car.
Bye bye!
We are going to ride Splash Mountain!
Splash Splash!
This is the scariest one.
Is it?
When we were on the slide, Piyo and I
were told to ride it.
But we didn't.
We didn't.
We didn't?
And we rode the big sand twice.
Right.
We were not good at it at that time.
We were not good at it.
We overcame it a little.
But I'm a little scared.
What should I do?
We fall down with our luggage.
Right.
We can ride it with our luggage.
Look!
We can ride it.
We fell down again.
I want to ride it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We are going to ride it.
How was it?
Splash Mountain was the best!
I was worried if I could go home alive.
I wanted to take a video of you while
you were riding.
But Hitoka was like,
I'm falling!
Action! I'm falling!
I was like,
I was in the middle of something.
I was so excited.
How many times?
Three times?
Two times?
It's too much!
It's okay. Everyone is alive.
If you want to eat churros, this way.
Churros, yes.
I'm going to eat churros.
It's a little cool.
Bye-bye.
Please subscribe to the channel.
We are going to ride Space Mountain!
We ate Churros just now.
Yes, it was a limited Churros with
chocolate flavor.
It was delicious.
We are going to ride Space Mountain.
We have decided our pair.
Julia, Kanami, Aki, and Shioharu.
Thank you.
Can you hear this sound?
Aki is taking a picture of us.
It's a recording. It's a recording.
It's a very dark and blue recording.
Space is like a dark place.
This is scary.
It's like a dot.
It's like a dot. That's scary.
It's warm and warm.
When this is over, it's a little
greener.
That's right.
Then, switch.
Switch.
Then, I'll go to the space station.
See you later.
The last day of the tour.
It's over.
The end.
It was so fast.
It was fun.
How many laps did we run?
But we lost half of the time.
We asked Julia to lend us her hand.
But one of us lost the hand.
It's not stable.
I heard Theo's scream.
I screamed a lot.
But it was fun.
It was fun.
Next is Little Green Man.
Are you ready?
Please subscribe to this channel!
We're going to perform at It's a Small
World!
Yay!
Oh, right!
Long time no see!
I'm sure I'll want to drink something
when I come to Disney!
I love it!
I'm sure I'll want to drink something
when I come to Disney!
We're taking pictures and videos of
each other.
Nice! You're cute, Kanami!
We're at the same aisle!
What is this?
Small world is a ride where you can sit
and enjoy.
You float in the water.
It's a beautiful image.
It's totally different from space.
It's totally different.
Space was crazy.
It was fast.
It's nice.
Even a small child can relax.
Let's talk a lot and ride!
We're going to line up.
Bye-bye!
Please subscribe to this channel!
We are going to ride the Hontetou
Mansion.
The baby fell down.
How is it?
It's cold now, so I want to go inside.
According to the rumor, it takes about
15 minutes to get there.
It's so fast.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a little early for afternoon
conversation.
I believed that there was a thousandth
ghost when I was in elementary school.
I thought I would be the thousandth
ghost.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to be chosen.
I can have a lot of dreams.
Please subscribe to my channel.
We are at the haunted mansion.
We are here.
We were healed by the picture of It's a
small world.
It was so cute.
The pictures were so cute.
The space was painted pastel color.
It was like a new world.
The last picture was so cute.
I want the white and light blue.
I want it.
It was cute.
It was like a winter snow.
How about you, Kikuri?
It's not winter yet.
It might be.
It's fun.
It's like poncho.
I like snow.
I want to wear a costume like snow
dome.
How about the space costume?
Snow dome?
It's like a space.
We are in the space.
How about the costume?
What do you mean?
It's like a space.
We wear it when we go to space.
We are in the dome.
It's like a new world.
It's like a snow.
It's so funny.
We have a lot of opinions.
We are in front of the haunted mansion.
It's getting cold outside.
So, if we eat this...
If we eat this...
We will be hungry.
What do you want to eat?
I want to go to the place where we went
to B-MAX.
Hamburger.
Those who are trying to eat the haunted
mansion.
If we eat this...
Some people are eating it.
I want to eat it.
That's right.
I will mix it.
Is it like this?
We are going to go.
We are going to enjoy it.
Bye bye.
We just had dinner.
Now, Tanamin, Hiyorin and Aki are in
the back seat.
We are full.
Tanamin and Hiyorin and I ate a fried
chicken burger.
It was crispy.
This was also crispy.
It was delicious.
We ate a large-sized burger.
What about you, Aki?
I ate a large-sized burger and a fried
chicken burger.
I ate a large-sized burger.
I ate a large-sized burger and a fried
chicken burger.
It was delicious.
I think chicken nuggets and croquettes
are a little bit the same.
But, they are totally different.
They are crispy and moist.
They were delicious.
I ate a churros.
I ate a chocolate flavor just now.
This time, I ate a plain flavor with
cinnamon.
They were crispy.
We enjoyed the food at Disney Land.
It was delicious.
I ate a custard flavor.
I ate a chocolate flavor.
I ate a strawberry flavor.
They are totally different.
There are three flavors.
I ate a little green man.
I think it is a little green man.
It was cold and delicious.
How did you like the chocolate flavor?
It was chocolate cream.
Why?
It was delicious.
It was soft.
I ate a strawberry flavor.
I ate an ice cream flavor.
It was sweet.
I thought it was a Thai-style.
The cream inside was sweet.
The custard flavor was like a raw Thai-
style.
I forgot what I wanted to say.
I forgot.
What?
It was not hard, but it was soft.
It was cold.
It was delicious.
Disney Land is the best.
What are we going to do next?
Shopping?
We are going to a souvenir shop.
What should we buy?
I want to buy a chocolate crunch.
It is a classic.
We can buy it together.
It is fun.
Let's decide.
We look forward to it.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.
We just finished dinner
Please tell us how you felt about
dinner
How was dinner?
Baymax was delicious
Baymax was delicious?
It was delicious
Was it delicious?
Eggs were overflowing
Baymax was delicious
I'm scared
It's cold
It's shining
It's true
I didn't say that much
I said
What do you want?
It's shining
I got a bite of a human
I got a bite of a BMAX burger
It's the same thing as the BMAX burger
It's brownie
It was good
Everyone is feeling cold right now
Do you want to take a picture of
everyone at Cinderella Castle?
Let's take a picture in a 6-person room
I'm going to buy a souvenir and go out
Bye bye
I'm going to take a picture of the
sunset.
We enjoyed ourselves!
It was fun!
It was so fulfilling!
It was so fun!
It was my first time to come to Disney.
So I was excited.
We had a lot of attractions.
We rode a lot of rides.
We ate a lot.
It was a fulfilling day.
How many steps did we walk?
I walked 18,000 steps.
We walked a lot.
We are exhausted.
We had a great time.
We will do our best for the rehearsal.
We are so happy.
We got a new barometer.
We will do our best to get a new
barometer.
If you think Disney is the best,
please push good button and subscribe
to our channel.
Please leave a comment.
See you next time.
Bye bye.
See you.
Disney is the best.
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is so colorful
Drawing a fragment of the future on the
canvas of my damaged heart
It will guide me
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I remember the time we met
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, playing
the sound of rain drops
I'm playing the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye
The city lights after the rain shine on
me from yesterday
My heart is like a flower, I'll dry my
tears
And wear a rainbow dress